The place where I see agents screwing up
work quite often is when it
comes to
abstraction design, system design, how
abstractions in a system go
together.
Effect has probably the most novel
dependency injection system that I've
worked with. And I've worked in enterprise
languages like Java, done the
whole Spring system. I've worked with
NestJS.
Effect's dependency injection is genuinely
fantastic and really, really
nice to work with. So because of this,
this is another feature that
encourages both agents and the developers
driving agents to
basically model programs in a type-driven
way.
Because you kind of define these things
called services and then
services get implementations and they can
get dependency injected.
So it really forces like the upfront work
of designing your system's composability
and
abstractions into the type system before
implementation ever occurs.